Finding Aid for Post Family Papers 1882-1973
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- C.W. Post
  - Alphabetical File
    - Post currency reform proposal
      - 1898 (Box 4)
        [4-7]
      - 1902 (Box 4)
        [4-8]
      - 1903 (Box 4)
        [4-9]
      - 1904 (Box 4)
        [4-10]
      - 1905 (Box 4)
        [4-11]
      - 1906 (Box 4)
        [4-12]
      - 1907 (Box 4)
        [4-13]
      - Undated (Box 4)
        [4-14]
    - Post, Ella M (divorce settlement) (Box 4)
      [4-15]
    - Post Land Co., Battle Creek (Box 4)
      [4-16]
    - Post, Marjorie (to 1914) (Box 4)
      [4-17; 4-18]
    - Post Theatre (Box 4)
      [4-19]
    - Post, Truman (Box 4)
      [4-20]
    - Postum Company (Factory matters) (Box 4)
      [4-21]
    - Postum Company, London (Box 4)
      [4-22]
    - Presidential election of 1908 (Box 4)
      [4-23]
    - Pure Food Laws (Box 4)
      [4-24]
    - Rainmaking Experiment in Battle Creek (Box 4)
      [4-25]
    - Sentinel Box
      - Correspondence (Box 4)
        [4-26]
      - Press releases (Box 4)
        [4-27]
    - Sherman Anti-trust Act (as applied to trade unions) (Box 4)
      [4-28]
    - Square Deal Magazine
      - 1904-1905 (Box 4)
        [4-29]
      - January-June 1906 (Box 4)
        [4-30]
      - July-December 1906 (Box 4)
        [4-31]
      - 1907 (Box 4)
        [4-32]
      - 1908 (Box 4)
        [4-33]
      - 1913-1914 (Box 4)
        [4-34]
      - Printed copies (Box 4)
        [4-35]
    - Trades and Workers Association of Battle Creek (Box 4)
      [4-36]
  - Post, Charles W. (personal)
    - Biographical (Box 2)
      [2-28; 2-29]
    - Correspondence
      - Personal (Box 2)
        [2-30]
      - With family (Box 2)
        [2-31]
    - Financial matters
      - 1882-1889 (Box 2)
        [2-32]
      - 1899 (bankruptcy) (Box 2)
        [2-33]
      - 1900-1906 (Box 2)
        [2-34]
      - 1907 (Box 2)
        [2-35]
      - 1908-1909 (Box 2)
        [2-36]
      - 1910-1913 (Box 2)
        [2-37]
      - 1914 (will and estate) (Box 2)
        [2-38; 2-39]
    - Funeral of C.W. Post (Box 2)
      [2-40]
    - Tributes and banquets of appreciation (5 v.) (Box 4)
      [4-1, etc. to 4-5]
    - C.W. Post Funeral
      - Tributes (primarily typescripts of correspondence, 3 volumes (Box 9)
      - Memorials (2 v.) (Box 9)
      - Scrapbook (primarily newspaper clippings) (Box 9)
      - Newspaper clippings (Box 9)
    - C.W. Post estate
      - Probate material (Box 45)
    - Investment summary sheets 1910-1914 (Box 45)
    - Postum Company
      - Copies of minutes and articles of association (Box 45)
      - Liability cases (Box 45)
      - Miscellanea (Box 45)
    - Real estate record 1906 (Box 45)
      [see also outsize vol.]
    - Fort Worth Paper Company (Box 45)
    - Fort Worth Woolen Mills (Box 45)
    - Summary statements of personal financial books 1912 (Box 45)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 45)
    - Lavita Inn (Box 46)
      - Ledgers and journal 1900-1906, 5 volumes (Box 46)
      - Minutes, articles of association, annual reports, and related material (Box 46)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 46)
    - Personal financial ledger 1901-1904 (Box 46)
      [see also outsize volumes]
  - Employer Organizations
    - Citizens Industrial Association of America
      - 1903 (Box 1)
        [1-15]
      - 1904 (Box 1)
        [1-16]
      - 1905 (Box 1)
        [1-17]
      - 1906 (Box 1)
        [1-18]
      - 1907 (Box 1)
        [1-19]
      - 1907 (Convention in Battle Creek, Mi.) (Box 1)
        [1-20]
      - January-June 1908 (Box 1)
        [1-21]
      - July 1908-1911 (Box 1)
        [1-22]
    - National Association of Manufacturers
      - 1904 (Box 1)
        [1-38]
      - 1905 (Box 1)
        [1-39]
      - 1906 (Box 1)
        [1-40]
      - January-June 1907 (Box 1)
        [1-41]
      - July-December 1907 (Box 1)
        [1-42]
      - January-June 1908 (Box 1)
        [1-43]
      - July-December 1908 (Box 1)
        [1-44]
      - January-October 1909 (Box 2)
        [2-1]
      - November-December 1909 (Box 2)
        [2-2]
      - January-April 1910 (Box 2)
        [2-3]
      - May-December 1910 (Box 2)
        [2-4]
      - 1911 (Box 2)
        [2-5]
      - Child Labor Committee (Box 2)
        [2-6]
      - Employers Liability and Workman's Compensation (Box 2)
        [2-7]
      - Membership rolls 1905-1911 (Box 2)
        [2-8]
      - Printed material
        - 1905-1906 (Box 2)
          [2-9]
        - 1906-1912 (Box 2)
          [2-10]
        - 1913 (Box 2)
          [2-11]
      - Miscellaneous (Box 2)
        [2-12]
    - National Council for Industrial Defence
      - 1908 (Box 2)
        [2-13]
      - 1909 (Box 2)
        [2-14]
      - 1910 (Box 2)
        [2-15]
      - 1912 (Box 2)
        [2-16]
  - Speeches, pamphlets and publications
    - Dated
      - 1894 (Box 3)
        - I Am Well (Box 3)
          [3-1]
      - 1902-1903
        [3-2]
        - December 2, 1902 "E. and E. Union; Employers and Employees United" (Box 3)
        - March 25, 1903 Untitled article on labor unions (Box 3)
        - October 14, 1903 "The Preliminary Training of an Advertiser" (Box 3)
      - 1904
        [3-3]
        - January 29: "How to Make a Halo" (positive image for products) (Box 3)
        - February 19: "Classify Criminals" (Box 3)
        - March 4: Untitled re workmen (Box 3)
        - March 7: Untitled re workmen (Box 3)
        - October 18: Untitled re labor in Battle Creek (Box 3)
        - October 22: "Prosperity and Peace vs. Labor Unionism" (Box 3)
        - November 29: "Industrial Peace" (Box 3)
        - December 4: "Absolute Balance of Employer and Employee" (Box 3)
      - 1905
        - January 13: "Our Errand Boy" re postoffice (Box 3)
          [3-4]
        - May 1: "Proclamation of Liberty" (including subsequent correspondence about the article)
          - May 1-5 (Box 3)
            [3-5]
          - May 6 (Box 3)
            [3-6]
          - May 7-30 (Box 3)
            [3-7]
          - June-August (Box 3)
            [3-8]
      - 1905
        [3-9]
        - May 20: "Who is the Owner" (Box 3)
        - May 24: Untitled re employment of suitable workers (Box 3)
        - July: "You are Your Brother's Keeper" (Box 3)
        - July: "The Common People" (Box 3)
        - September 7: "Report to the People" re labor unions (Box 3)
        - November 15: "Controlled by Citizens. Both Labor and Capital Trusts Must be Governed by the People." (Box 3)
        - December 30" Address to employees at annual banquet (2 copies and press clippings) (Box 3)
      - 1906
        [3-10]
        - Undated: "A Message from the Food Expert to Physicians" (Box 3)
        - January 15: "Patriotism and Pocketbooks" (Box 3)
        - January 30: Untitled re street car employees (Box 3)
        - March: "The Chief Offender" re American Federation of Labor (Box 3)
        - May: "The Men Between the Two Mill Stones" (Box 3)
        - July 4: "To Mongrels, Tyrants, Slaves and Freemen" (Box 3)
        - October 9: article re newspapers (Box 3)
        - October 16: article re industrial paternalism (Box 3)
        - October 19 editorial re proposed bond issue for Battle Creek (Box 3)
        - December 3: "Progress in Industrial Freedom in 1906" (Box 3)
          (manuscript, printed text and newspaper reports)
        - December 14: re Dr. Kellogg (Box 3)
        - December 29: Address to Employees at Annual Banquet (Box 3)
      - 1907
        [3-11]
        - Undated: "The Better Day" (Box 3)
        - Undated: re labor unions (Box 3)
        - Undated: re politicians attacking "middle-men" as cause of high prices" (Box 3)
        - Undated: "Unto One of the Least of These" (Box 3)
        - Undated: "The Fundamental Principles of a Great Party should be based upon equal opportunity for all" (Box 3)
        - January 8: Address to Battle Creek Business Men's Association (Box 3)
        - February 6: re Texas Lands (Box 3)
        - March 8: re mayor (Box 3)
        - March 16: re Battle Creek election (Box 3)
        - August 20: re "Pageant of St. Albans" in England (Box 3)
        - October 1: re Post's reputation as a "union buster" (Box 3)
        - October 7: Address to National Citizen's Industrial Conference (manuscript, typescript and press release) (Box 3)
      - 1908
        [3-12]
        - Undated re Tyranny and rights related to labor unions (Box 3)
        - February 12: re proposed legislation that jeopardizes property rights (Box 3)
        - April 12: Profit-sharing in Battle Creek (Box 3)
        - July 16: re workmen (Box 3)
        - August 12: "There's a Reason" re advertising (Box 3)
        - September 5: "Trust Control" (Box 3)
        - October: "$1000.00 Reward" (Box 3)
        - November 16: re workmen (Box 3)
        - December 3: Address before the Battle Creek Industrial Association (Box 3)
      - 1909
        [3-13]
        - Undated: "Union Knocking" (Box 3)
        - January 20: re Association of American Advertisers (Box 3)
        - May1: re Future of Battle Creek (Box 3)
        - September 16: re harmful newspapers (Box 3)
        - October 12: re narcotics (Box 3)
      - 1910
        [3-14]
        - Undated "The Prodigal's Return" (Box 3)
        - January: "The Churches and the Labor Trust" (Box 3)
        - January 20: Address to the Association of American Advertisers" (Box 3)
        - January 31: "An Advertiser's Duty to the Public" (Box 3)
        - March 20: "'Punishing' Battle Creek The Paid Agents of the Labor Trust are Making Good Their Threat: (Box 3)
        - June 29: re personal experience in advertising (Box 3)
        - July 1: "The Reason of Postum" (Box 3)
        - September 7: re Politicians pandering to unions (Box 3)
      - 1911
        [3-15]
        - August 5: "Property Rights" (Box 3)
        - August 31: "To Railroad Men" (Box 3)
        - October 5: re Farmers and labor unions (Box 3)
        - December 11: Open letter to Samuel Gompers (Box 3)
      - 1912
        [3-16]
        - Undated: re operation of sanitarium (Box 3)
        - Undated: re attraction of Battle Creek for workers (Box 3)
        - Undated: "Folk Songs" (Box 3)
        - Undated: re Tyranny of labor unions (Box 3)
        - Undated: Comments do press humorists (Box 3)
      - 1913
        [3-17]
        - Undated: "The Blending of Art with Commerce" (Box 3)
        - Undated: "A Pathway to Peace" (Box 3)
        - March 18: "A Hill of Roses" (Box 3)
        - March 18: "No More Rations, Putting the Mob Makers on Short Feed" (Box 3)
        - May 22: A Peaceful Industrial Family" (Box 3)
        - June 10: "Inside History" (Box 3)
        - August 24: "Human Happiness" (Box 3)
        - September 29: Remarks at dinner in Post's honor (Box 3)
    - Undated
      - A-E
        [3-18]
        - " A Boycott" (Box 3)
        - "Reply to Boycott: A Bit of Straight Talk to Unions" (Box 3)
        - "Result of Boycott" (Box 3)
        - "Challenges Chicago Federation of Labor" (Box 3)
        - "Controlled by Citizens; Both Labor and Capital Trusts Must be Governed by the People" (Box 3)
        - "Counter Movements to Political Programme of Organized Labor" (Box 3)
        - "Don't Weep at the Ice House" (Box 3)
        - "Eight Hour Day" (2 speeches) (Box 3)
        - "Equality Thieves" (Box 3)
      - F-M
        [3-19]
        - "Free Riot" 'Laws'" (Box 3)
        - "Grievances" (Box 3)
        - "Industrial Investment vs. Stock Speculation" (Box 3)
        - "The Labor Trust" (Box 3)
        - "Labor Trust Responsible for Panic" (Box 3)
        - "Labor Unions vs. Farmers Opposing Interests" (Box 3)
        - "A Letter to the President" (Box 3)
        - "Levelers, The Mission of Whiskey, Tobacco and Coffee" (Box 3)
        - "Local Option" (Box 3)
        - "Look Under It" (Box 3)
        - " A Message of Peace" (Box 3)
        - "Mollycoddling by Congressmen" of unions" (Box 3)
      - N-P
        [3-20]
        - National Association of Manufacturers (address before) (Box 3)
        - "A Newspaper's responsibility to the Public" (Box 3)
        - "Not for the Sleepy" (Box 3)
        - "On Man" (Box 3)
        - "Parasites" (Box 3)
        - "Property Rights" (Box 3)
        - "The Preliminary Training of an Advertiser" (Box 3)
        - "Prosperity Makers vs. Wreckers" (Box 3)
        - "Pull off the Cover" (Box 3)
      - Q-Z
        [3-21]
        - "The Real Voting Power Held by the Citizens and Not by the Trusts" (Box 3)
        - "Reasons Why" (Box 3)
        - "The Second Man" (Box 3)
        - "A Simple Tale of a Town" (Box 3)
        - "Sketch of Uncle Sam in Speakers Chair in House of Congress" (Box 3)
        - "Some of the Tales Told at the Postum Family Supper" (Box 3)
        - "A Square Deal to Both Sides" (Box 3)
        - "Story of the Shoemakers. A Fireside Tale" (Box 3)
        - "Strike Rights of Employers and Employees" (Box 3)
        - "Taxes" (Box 3)
        - "There Was a Little Man" (Box 3)
        - "They Do Things" (Box 3)
        - "To the Working Men of Chicago" (Box 3)
        - "Whacks and What They Mean" (Box 3)
        - "Words of a Statesman" (Box 3)
      - Road to Wellville (selection of advertising copy put together and reissued in 1926) (Box 3)
        [3-22]
    - Untitled
      - untitled (Box 3)
        [3-23; etc. to 3-27]
    - "Letters to the Editor" (Box 3)
      [3-28]
  - Letterbooks and scrapbooks
    - Letterbooks (Box 5)
      - 1889-1890 (Box 5)
      - 1895-1899 (Box 5)
        (original and photocopy)
    - Personal scrapbooks
      - 1902-1903 (Box 5)
      - 1904-1905 (Box 5)
      - 1906-1908 (Box 6)
    - Business scrapbook 1902-1908 (Box 6)
    - Scrapbook 1903-1904 (Box 6)
      (largely concerning conventions of the National Association of Manufacturers, labor disputes)
    - Scrapbook 1902-1906 (Box 6)
      (largely concerning Post check currency)
    - Scrapbook 1905-1912 (Box 7)
    - Scrapbook (Box 8)
      - 1907-1913 (Box 8)
      - 1911-1915 (Volume 1)
  - Ledgers and Journals 1906-1921
    - Journal Entry Record Book
      - October 1908-January 1910 (Volume 42)
        [42]
        [special location: B 302/5]
      - February 1910-April 1911 (Volume 43)
        [43]
      - April 1911-June 1912 (Volume 44)
        [44]
        [special location: B 302/6]
      - July 1912-May 1914 (Volume 45)
        [45]
      - May 1913-May 1914 (Volume 46)
        [46]
        [special location: B 302/7]
      - May 1914-December 1918 (Volume 47)
        [47]
        [special location: B 302/8]
      - December 1918-September 1920 (Volume 48)
        [48]
        [special location: B 302/9]
    - Personal Journal (financial)
      - October 1904-May 1906 (Volume 49)
        [49]
      - May 1906-September 1907 (Volume 50)
        [50]
      - September 1907-November 1907 (Volume 51)
        [51]
      - November 1907-May 1908 (Volume 52)
        [52]
        [special location: B 302/10]
      - May 1908-September 1908 (Volume 53)
        [53]
    - Ledger (accounts receivable and payable)
      - October 1908-October 1911 (Volume 54)
        [54]
      - October 1911-April 1913 (Volume 55)
        [55]
      - April 1913-May 1914 (Volume 56)
        [56]
      - May 1914-1920 (Volume 57)
        [57]
    - Ledger (investments)
      - October 1908-August 1912 (Volume 58)
        [58]
      - August 1912-1921 (Volume 59)
        [59]
    - Ledger (earnings and expenses)
      - October 1908-April 1913 (Volume 60)
        [60]
        [special location: B 302/11]
      - April 1913-1920 (Volume 61)
        [61]
    - General Ledger
      - April 1907-October 1908 (Volume 62)
        [62]
    - Stock Register
      - circa 1909-1915 (Volume 63)
        [63]
    - Bond Register
      - circa 1902-1913 (Volume 64)
        [64]
    - Real Estate Rentals
      - circa 1904-1906 (Volume 65)
        [65]
        [special location: B 302/12]
    - Ledger (construction projects)
      - 3-E (Volume 66)
        [66]
      - 4-E (Volume 67)
        [67]
    - Ledger (loans)
      - 1905-1911 (Volume 68)
        [68]
      - 1911-1916 (Volume 69)
        [69]
        [special location: B 302/13]
    - Ledger (rents)
      - 1908-1914 (Volume 70)
        [70]
    - Ledger (miscellaneous)
      - Bonds, real estate, loans, stocks, etc. circa 1902-1909 (Volume 71)
        [71]
- Marjorie M. Post
  The papers of Marjorie Merriweather Post generally reflect the last years of her life, from approximately 1955 until her death. Consisting primarily of material about her collected by her staff, communications between various staff members regarding the inordinate amount of housekeeping necessary to maintain Post's various estates and lifestyle, and occasionally direct requests by the staff for Mrs. Post's opinion or orders, the papers tell more of Marjorie Post's lifestyle than they do of the woman herself. Much more interesting, but much less common, are documents created by Post herself, generally dating before 1955.
  - Correspondence
    The Marjorie Post series includes a small amount of correspondence with members of her father's and mother's family. There is also correspondence with E.F. Hutton, members of his family, and with Hutton's and Post's daughter, Dina Merrill. Most revealing is a file of intimate correspondence between Post and Joseph Davies. The documents are, however, purely personal, and although many date from the years of Davies' service as ambassador to the U.S.S.R., they are almost totally devoid of political commentary.
    - Letters of Joseph Davies to Marjorie Post
      (formerly in scrapbooks, listing for each folder gives inclusive dates, page numbers and folder number)
      - March-May 1935 (Box 10)
        [pages 1-10; folder 10-1]
      - May-June 1935 (Box 10)
        [pages 11-20; folder 10-2]
      - June-September 1935 (Box 10)
        [pages 21-30; folder 10-3]
      - September 1935 (Box 10)
        [pages 31-40; folder 10-4]
      - October-November 1935 (Box 10)
        [pages 34-50; folder 10-5]
      - December 1935 (Box 10)
        [pages 51-60; folder 10-6]
      - 1935 undated January-May 1936 (Box 10)
        [pages 61-70; folder 10-7]
      - May 1936 (Box 10)
        [pages 71-80; folder 10-8]
      - May-December 1936 (Box 10)
        [pages 81-90; folder 10-9]
      - January-July 1937 (Box 10)
        [pages 1-15; folder 10-10]
      - July-October 1937 (Box 10)
        [pages 16-30; folder 10-11]
      - October 1937 (Box 10)
        [pages 31-45; folder 10-12]
      - October 1937 (Box 10)
        [pages 46-60; folder 10-13]
      - October 1937 (Box 10)
        [pages 61-70; folder 10-14]
      - October-November 1937 (Box 10)
        [pages 71-90; folder 10-15]
      - November 1937 (Box 10)
        [pages 91-100; folder 10-16]
      - November-December 1937 (Box 10)
        [pages 101-121; folder 10-17]
      - January-April 1938 (Box 10)
        [pages 1-15; folder 10-18]
      - June-October 1938 (Box 10)
        [pages 16-30; folder 10-19]
      - October 1938 (Box 10)
        [pages 31-47; folder 10-20]
      - October 1938 (Box 10)
        [pages 48-60; folder 10-21]
      - October-November 1938 (Box 10)
        [pages 61-81; folder 10-22]
      - January-June 1939 (Box 10)
        [pages 1-15; folder 10-23]
      - June 1939 (Box 10)
        [pages 16-30; folder 10-24]
      - June-July 1939 (Box 10)
        [pages 31-50; folder 10-25]
      - July-September 1939 (Box 10)
        [pages 51-71; folder 10-26]
      - September-October 1939 (Box 10)
        [pages 72-87; folder 10-27]
      - October 1939 (Box 10)
        [pages 88-100; folder 10-28]
      - October 1939 (Box 10)
        [pages 101-115; folder 10-29]
    - Letters of Joseph Davies to Marjorie Post (Box 11)
      - October-November 1939 (Box 11)
        [pages 116-130; folder 11-1]
      - November 1939 (Box 11)
        [pages 131-145; folder 11-2]
      - November-December 1939 (Box 11)
        [pages 146-160; folder 11-3]
      - December 1939-May 1940 (Box 11)
        [pages 161-185; folder 11-4]
      - May-August 1940 (Box 11)
        [11-5]
      - September-December 1940 (Box 11)
        [11-6]
      - January-June 1941 (Box 11)
        [11-7]
      - July 1941 (Box 11)
        [11-8]
      - August-December 1941 (Box 11)
        [11-9]
      - 1942 (Box 11)
        [11-10]
      - January-March 1943 (Box 11)
        [11-11]
      - April-May 1943 (Box 11)
        [11-12]
      - June-December 1943 (Box 11)
        [11-13]
    - Letters of Joseph Davies to Marjorie Post (Box 12)
      - Cables and telegrams
        - Undated (Box 12)
          [12-1]
        - September 1946-September 1949 (Box 12)
          [12-2]
      - Cards
        - Undated (Box 12)
          [12-3; 12-4]
      - Letters
        - Undated (Box 12)
          [12-5]
        - July 1947 (Box 12)
          [12-6]
        - October-December 1947 (Box 12)
          [12-7]
        - 1948 (Box 12)
          [12-8]
        - January-May 1949 (Box 12)
          [12-9]
        - June 1949 (Box 12)
          [12-10]
        - July 1949 (Box 12)
          [12-11]
        - August-December 1949 (Box 12)
          [12-12]
        - January-June 1950 (Box 12)
          [12-13]
        - July-December 1950 (Box 12)
          [12-14]
        - January-April 1951 (Box 12)
          [12-15]
        - May 1951 (Box 12)
          [12-16]
        - June-December 1951 (Box 12)
          [12-17]
        - 1952-1954 (Box 12)
          [12-18]
    - Letters of Marjorie M. Post to Joseph E. Davies
      - Letters
        - Undated (Box 12)
          [12-19; etc. to 12-22]
        - January-April 1935 (Box 12)
          [12-23]
        - May 1935 (Box 12)
          [12-24]
        - June-July 1935 (Box 12)
          [12-25]
        - August 1935 (Box 12)
          [12-26]
        - September-December 1935 (Box 12)
          [12-27]
        - 1939-1940 (Box 12)
          [12-28]
      - Notes from Joseph E. Davies to Marjorie M. Post ("Little Love Notes"). undated (Box 12)
    - Personal correspondence
      - Undated (Box 13)
        [13-1, etc. to 13-3]
      - 1916-June 1918 (Box 13)
        [13-4]
      - July 1918-1919 (Box 13)
        [13-5]
      - 1921-1926 (Box 13)
        [13-6]
      - 1927 (Box 13)
        [13-7]
      - 1928 (Box 13)
        [13-8]
      - 1932-1933 (Box 13)
        [13-9]
      - 1934-1938 (Box 13)
        [13-10]
      - January-June 1939 (Box 13)
        [13-11]
      - July-December 1939 (Box 13)
        [13-12]
      - 1940-1942 (Box 13)
        [13-13]
    - Letters of condolences on mother's death
      - Undated (Box 13)
        [13-14, etc. to 13-16]
      - October 22, 1912 (Box 13)
        [13-17]
      - October 23, 1912 (Box 13)
        [13-18]
      - October 24, 1912 (Box 13)
        [13-19]
      - October 25-31, 1912 (Box 13)
        [13-20]
      - November 1-11, 1912 (Box 13)
        [13-21]
      - November 12, 1912-February 9, 1913 (Box 13)
        [13-22]
    - Letters of condolences on father's death
      - Undated (Box 13)
        [13-23, etc. to 13-25]
      - May 9-11, 1914, Undated (Box 13)
        [13-26]
      - May 12-15, 1914 (Box 13)
        [13-27]
      - May 16-24, 1914 (Box 13)
        [13-28]
      - May 25-June 26, 1914 (Box 13)
        [13-29]
    - Letters from Mrs. Carroll L. Post
      - 1907-1923 (Box 13)
        [13-30]
      - 1924-1928 (Box 13)
        [13-31]
    - Letters to Mrs. Carroll L. Post
      - Undated (Box 13)
        [13-32]
      - 1899-1901 (Box 13)
        [13-33]
    - Letters from and about C. Rollins Post
      - 1916-1918 (Box 13)
        [13-34]
    - Letters from C.W. Post
      - 1902-1909 (Box 13)
        [13-35]
    - Letters to and about Edward .B. Close (Box 13)
      [13-36]
  - Alphabetical file
    The Alphabetical File includes correspondence, reports and other material relating to Marjorie Posts social life and philanthropic activities.